IMGID:16_05_16_323
Tonight	O
was	O
incredible	O
!	O
#	O
LCFCParade	B-MISC
#	O
havingaparty	O
#	O
LCFCChampions	O
#	O
WeAreLeicester	O

IMGID:16_05_18_79
When	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
best	O
friend	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
baseball	O
game	O
:	O
⚾	O
️	O

IMGID:16_05_22_477
Something	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
'	O
d	O
never	O
do	O
:	O
attend	O
a	O
football	O
match	O
.	O
Oxford	B-ORG
versus	O
Watford	B-ORG
Ladies	I-ORG
,	O
since	O
you	O
didn	O
'	O
t	O
ask	O
.	O

IMGID:16_05_25_859
@	O
adamlambert	B-PER
I	O
love	O
ur	O
costumes	O
for	O
the	O
concerts	O
!	O
You	O
'	O
re	O
really	O
superstar	O
🌟	O
#	O
GLAMBERTS	O

IMGID:17_06_13629
18	O
days	O
til	O
I	O
see	O
my	O
love	O
in	O
concert	O
💗	O
@	O
ShawnMendes	B-PER

IMGID:16_05_28_57
#	O
MVCBaseball	B-MISC
Championship	I-MISC
:	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
lineups	O
for	O
the	O
game	O
!	O
First	O
pitch	O
just	O
thrown	O
!	O
#	O
HereWeGo	O

IMGID:17_06_15911
Father	O
'	O
s	O
NBA	B-ORG
Success	O
Inspired	O
Kevin	B-PER
Stefanski	I-PER
to	O
NFL	B-ORG
Career	O

IMGID:O_2635
Kevin	B-PER
Durant	I-PER
had	O
17	O
of	O
his	O
41	O
points	O
in	O
the	O
4	O
th	O
quarter	O
,	O
outscoring	O
the	O
entire	O
Spurs	B-ORG
team	O
.	O

IMGID:O_1747
Harry	B-PER
Styles	I-PER
is	O
like	O
biggest	O
and	O
cutest	O
dork	O
in	O
the	O
world	O

IMGID:O_3448
countdown	O
💜	O
-	O
357	O
days	O
until	O
Harry	B-PER
Styles	I-PER
Live	O
On	O
Tour	O

IMGID:17_06_14475
German	B-LOC
youth	O
football	O
team	O
rallies	O
behind	O
'	O
star	O
players	O
'	O
facing	O
deportation	O

IMGID:17_06_262
Festival	O
season	O
got	O
you	O
in	O
need	O
of	O
"	O
drying	O
out	O
"	O
?	O
Why	O
not	O
try	O
our	O
Green	O
Tea	O
flavoured	O
Jelly	B-ORG
Belly	I-ORG
beans	O
#	O
jellybelly	B-ORG

IMGID:16_05_01_383
Rt	O
@	O
NBA	B-ORG
The	O
@	O
spurs	B-ORG
take	O
1	O
-	O
0	O
#	O
SPURSvTHUNDER	O
lead	O
with	O
124	O
-	O
92	O
W	O
on	O
Aldridge	B-PER
'	O
s	O
38	O
:	O

IMGID:17_06_2673
Great	O
fun	O
seeing	O
@	O
fredsshedmovie	B-MISC
at	O
The	B-MISC
Box	I-MISC
Film	I-MISC
Festival	I-MISC
on	O
Saturday	O
at	O
@	O
ArlingtonArts	B-LOC
!	O

IMGID:O_2815
Robert	B-PER
Downey	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	O
:	O
‘	O
Spider	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
Man	I-MISC
:	I-MISC
Homecoming	I-MISC
’	O
Early	O
Screenings	O
Did	O
Well	O

IMGID:17_06_13134
Watch	O
Swansea	B-ORG
FC	I-ORG
Football	I-ORG
Highlights	O
-	O

IMGID:16_05_20_979
Liverpool	B-ORG
and	O
Sevilla	B-ORG
under	O
investigation	O
by	O
UEFA	B-ORG
after	O
crowd	O
trouble	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

IMGID:16_05_08_307
happy	O
Mother	O
'	O
s	O
Day	O
to	O
all	O
of	O
our	O
lovely	O
mothers	O
who	O
have	O
watched	O
us	O
play	O
soccer	O
on	O
Mother	O
'	O
s	O
Day	O
for	O
3	O
yrs	O
in	O
a	O
row	O
💓	O
💓	O

IMGID:17_06_2634
3	O
CNN	B-ORG
Journalists	O
Resign	O
After	O
Retracted	O
Story	O
on	O
Trump	B-PER
Ally	O
by	O
MICHAEL	B-PER
M	I-PER
.	I-PER
GRYNBAUM	I-PER
via	O

IMGID:17_06_14698
Scouts	O
knew	O
Tom	B-PER
Brady	I-PER
was	O
special	O
…	O
in	O
baseball	O
➡	O
️	O

IMGID:16_05_02_349
You	O
'	O
ll	O
never	O
believe	O
it	O
Del	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
@	O
LCFC	B-ORG
have	O
won	O
the	O
@	O
premierleague	B-ORG
🏆	O
⚽	O
️	O
🙌	O
🏻	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
#	O
Champions	O

IMGID:O_1723
Ed	B-PER
Sheeran	I-PER
'	O
s	O
Carpool	B-MISC
Karaoke	I-MISC
is	O
coming	O
next	O
week	O
🎉	O

IMGID:16_05_30_572
#	O
festival	O
season	O
is	O
now	O
here	O
have	O
you	O
tried	O
Coachstar	O
for	O
an	O
unbeatable	O
deal	O
on	O
#	O
winnebagohire	O

IMGID:17_06_13222
One	O
hour	O
(	O
Portugal	B-LOC
time	O
)	O
till	O
dBs	O
Filmmaker	O
'	O
s	O
Corner	O
at	O
@	O
FESTFestival	B-MISC
!	O

IMGID:O_153
President	O
Obama	B-PER
shares	O
his	O
views	O
on	O
his	O
wife	O
Michelle	B-PER
Obama	I-PER
'	O
s	O
ageless	O
beauty	O

IMGID:17_06_7445
Can	O
You	O
Guess	O
The	O
Footballer	O
From	O
Their	O
Brand	O
Logos	O
?	O

IMGID:16_05_28_431
Saturday	O
night	O
fun	O
with	O
the	O
Devils	B-ORG
!	O
@	O
ASU_Baseball	B-ORG

IMGID:17_06_3490
Devolver	B-ORG
loses	O
$	O
100	O
K	O
on	O
banned	O
E3	B-MISC
festival	I-MISC

IMGID:O_145
31	O
plays	O
to	O
celebrate	O
Chris	B-PER
Paul	I-PER
(	O
@	O
CP3	O
)	O
'	O
s	O
31	O
st	O
birthday	O
:	O

IMGID:17_06_13949
Perfect	O
Boston	B-LOC
night	O
for	O
a	O
concert	O
.	O
Good	O
pickup	O
on	O
@	O
TickPick	B-ORG
for	O
the	O
@	O
BHBPavilion	B-LOC
!	O

IMGID:O_2052
#	O
Trump2016	O
West	B-ORG
Virginia	I-ORG
Coal	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
Endorses	O
Donald	B-PER
Trump	I-PER
over	O
Hillary	B-PER
,	O
…	O

IMGID:O_2078
BREAKING	O
:	O
Wayne	B-PER
Rooney	I-PER
has	O
had	O
his	O
iCloud	O
account	O
hacked	O
,	O
naked	O
pictures	O
released	O
.	O
.	O

IMGID:17_06_2184
The	O
NBA	B-ORG
Finals	O
:	O
Durant	B-PER
,	O
Curry	B-PER
lead	O
Warriors	B-ORG
to	O
Game	O
2	O
win	O
over	O
Cavs	B-ORG

IMGID:16_05_02_696
Harlem	B-LOC
’	O
s	O
Alicia	B-PER
Keys	I-PER
To	O
Debut	O
New	O
Music	O
At	O
UEFA	B-MISC
Final	O

IMGID:16_05_15_605
Manuel	B-PER
Pellegrini	I-PER
has	O
almost	O
certainly	O
secured	O
Champions	B-ORG
League	I-ORG
football	O
in	O
his	O
final	O
game	O
:	O

IMGID:16_05_16_1071
2016	O
Baseball	O
senior	O
day	O
at	O
Johnson	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
.	O
.	O
.	O
GO	O
Crusader	O
Nation	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

IMGID:O_912
The	O
house	O
that	O
Donald	B-PER
Trump	I-PER
couldn	O
’	O
t	O
buy	O
,	O
New	B-LOC
Jersey	I-LOC
,	O
1991	O

IMGID:O_3823
Shah	B-PER
Rukh	I-PER
Khan	I-PER
ditches	O
the	O
macho	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
new	O
'	O
chikna	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

IMGID:16_05_19_976
Need	O
some	O
festival	O
fun	O
?	O
Join	O
us	O
at	O
this	O
new	O
#	O
yoga	O
and	O
wellness	O
#	O
festival	O
in	O
the	O
Cotswolds	O
!	O

IMGID:17_06_14237
The	O
Medgar	B-PER
Evers	I-PER
parade	O
is	O
underway	O
in	O
the	O
Georgetown	B-LOC
community	O
of	O
Jackson	B-LOC

IMGID:17_01_18348
Top	O
Movies	O
Ever	O
Made	O
On	O
Soccer	O
-	O

IMGID:O_4429
If	O
a	O
thing	O
loves	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
infinite	O
.	O
-	O
William	B-PER
Blake	I-PER
#	O
lovequotes	O

IMGID:17_06_15974
Nice	O
night	O
for	O
@	O
LittleLeague	B-ORG
baseball	O
at	O
Bell	B-LOC
Mtn	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
in	O
@	O
huntsvillecity	B-LOC

IMGID:16_05_18_236
Mlb	B-ORG
&	O
gt	O
;	O
The	O
Cincinnati	B-ORG
Reds	I-ORG
'	O
bullpen	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
worst	O
in	O
baseball	O
histo	O
.	O
.	O

IMGID:16_05_08_873
Girls	O
’	O
flag	O
football	O
taking	O
important	O
steps	O
in	O
Saskatoon	B-LOC
#	O
TODAY	O

IMGID:O_3322
Calvin	B-ORG
Klein	I-ORG
NEW	O
Women	O
'	O
s	O
12	O
P	O
Petite	O
Watermelon	O
Cutout	O
Neck	O
Pleat	O
-	O
Side	O
Dress	O
#	O
189	O

IMGID:16_05_16_1007
nothing	O
better	O
than	O
bothering	O
your	O
mom	O
at	O
work	O
about	O
concerts	O
@	O
troyesivan	B-PER

IMGID:16_05_24_1
Recap	O
:	O
Oklahoma	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
Thunder	I-ORG
thump	O
Golden	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Warriors	I-ORG
to	O
take	O
3	O
-	O
1	O
series	O
lead	O
in	O
NBA	B-ORG
…	O

IMGID:17_06_1922
LETS	O
GOO	O
Game	O
2	O
#	O
NBAFinals	O
#	O
DubNation	B-ORG

IMGID:16_05_04_249
im	O
wearing	O
this	O
dress	O
2	O
my	O
schools	O
spring	O
concert	O
its	O
so	O
pretty	O
and	O
i	O
love	O
it	O
so	O
much	O

IMGID:16_05_02_410
Going	O
to	O
a	O
music	O
festival	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
next	O
month	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
choice	O
but	O
to	O
buy	O
this	O
right	O
?	O

IMGID:O_4763
Lobby	O
firm	O
tied	O
to	O
Barney	B-PER
Frank	I-PER
and	O
Nancy	B-PER
Pelosi	I-PER
uses	O
lefty	O
groups	O
to	O
help	O
hedge	O
funds	O

IMGID:16_05_05_952
Golden	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Warriors	I-ORG
Look	O
to	O
Break	O
20	O
-	O
Year	O
NBA	B-ORG
Record	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

